http://www.freefallexpress.com/privacy/

Close
Book Online Now!Buy Gift CertificatesContact Us
Call Us @ 417.882.JUMP or 800.598.JUMP
3103 Lawrence 1070, Suite 2, Miller, MO 65707 | Get Directions
Closed Friday
Weather
Reservations Info and Rates Book Online Gift Certificates First Time Tandem Skydiving Video Services Frequently Asked Questions Learn General Info Accelerated Free Fall Experienced General Info Links Local General Info Accommodations Restaurants Attractions About Testimonials Articles News Events Gallery Photos & Videos Photos Videos Contact Contact Us Now Weather Directions
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy
Ozarks Skydive Center is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Ozarks Skydive Center Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Ozarks Skydive Center website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Ozarks Skydive Center collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Ozarks Skydive Center also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Ozarks Skydive Center. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Ozarks Skydive Center for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Ozarks Skydive Center Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Ozarks Skydive Center public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Ozarks Skydive Center does not read any of your private online communications.
Ozarks Skydive Center encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Ozarks Skydive Center so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Ozarks Skydive Center is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Ozarks Skydive Center and Ozarks Skydive Center family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Ozarks Skydive Center collects and uses your personal information to operate the Ozarks Skydive Center Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Ozarks Skydive Center also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Ozarks Skydive Center and its affiliates. Ozarks Skydive Center may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Ozarks Skydive Center does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Ozarks Skydive Center may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Ozarks Skydive Center may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Ozarks Skydive Center, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Ozarks Skydive Center does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Ozarks Skydive Center keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Ozarks Skydive Center, in order to determine what Ozarks Skydive Center services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Ozarks Skydive Center to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Ozarks Skydive Center Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Ozarks Skydive Center or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Ozarks Skydive Center; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Ozarks Skydive Center, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Ozarks Skydive Center Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Ozarks Skydive Center pages, or register with Ozarks Skydive Center site or services, a cookie helps Ozarks Skydive Center to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Ozarks Skydive Center Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Ozarks Skydive Center features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Ozarks Skydive Center services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Ozarks Skydive Center secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Ozarks Skydive Center secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Ozarks Skydive Center will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Ozarks Skydive Center encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Ozarks Skydive Center is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Ozarks Skydive Center welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Ozarks Skydive Center has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Ozarks Skydive Center at ozarksskydive@gmail.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Options
Contact Privacy Policy Terms of Use Sitemap
Book Online Now!
Skydiving Info & Rates
Buy Gift Certificates
The owner and staff were awesome, and really made us feel comfortable.
Ozarks Skydive Center is a member of the United States Parachute Association.
Copyright © 2020, Ozarks Skydive Center, All Rights Reserved.
DropZone Web Design & Marketing by Beyond Marketing, LLC
